♪La la la la la la, la la la la la la♪
♪La la la la la la la la la♪
♪No matter what day it is,
I'll spend it with you♪
♪We're more sure
of each other than ever♪
=Watching Heart Signal with You=
(Before the watch-along starts)
(Leaning close)
Is my face really this round?
Your face isn't round at all.
Really?
Not round at all.
It's super round.
What am I gonna do?
Sit.
Meng.
This is so fun.
Si, Xing.
Do I look elegant sitting like this?
What about this?
Yes.
Based on last time's experience,
you'll look stiff sitting like that.
Last time I put my hands
on my knees.
I felt so awkward.
So how do we not look awkward?
Teach us.
Teach us, Si.
You two are just naturally relaxed.
I think she's the one
who looks unnatural.
Natural.
Last time I was sitting
all over the place.
Right?
You looked really natural. As soon
as I was next to her, I was like this.
Si is so cute.
When it cuts to you...
I sit up straight.
Especially when you said,
"It's a fairy, not a dragonfly."
Welcome to the watch-along.
Welcome.
This is our second time
doing the watch-along.
Yeah.
Mine too.
Hers too.
(Second time)
Welcome, Xing.
(Watch-along newbie arrives)
Let's introduce ourselves.
Hello everyone.
I'm Sun Qimeng
(Sun Qimeng)
from Heart Signal 9.
Hello everyone.
I'm Sha Yue'er
(Sha Yue'er)
from Heart Signal 9.
Hello everyone,
I'm Wu Xingying
(Wu Xingying)
from Heart Signal 9.
Hello everyone,
I'm Wu Siying
(Wu Siying)
from Heart Signal 9.
Meng, what was the last
watch-along you did?
(Curious)
It was the one at the playground.
The open day.
It was pretty touching.
You didn't cry during
the watch-along, did you?
How did you know?
You know me too well.
But I'm really looking forward
to today's episode.
I watched the previous episode.
So I roughly know
what's coming this time.
There'll be a double selection.
Yeah, it's the double-selection date.
Are you thirsty?
We can drink some water.
(Enjoy the food first)
Yeah.
We can eat, drink,
and watch at the same time.
I'll have this first.
I'm starving.
Didn't you eat earlier?
I did.
I'm just someone who gets hungry easily.
My mom always asks
why I look like I haven't eaten.
Does your mom always follow the show?
Do your parents watch it too?
She already finished today's episode.
Are both your moms the emotional type?
Very emotional.
She said she laughed and cried today.
When she saw Xing smiling,
and then saw me go find her,
she started crying.
There's no way we're going
to finish this whole plate
before we start watching.
This might be the most
food-filled watch-along.
Then we'll finish everything.
This episode got stuck
with the four of us.
Too bad for it.
This is how you are, Xing?
She's honestly funny sometimes.
How about we...
Let's get started.
I'm so excited.
Let's start.
We're back.
This is after we came back
from that event.
Yeah.
You look like a greeter.
Our returning group
(Your hands...)
is way too big.
(Imitating)
Put them here.
You understood that?
I didn't understand you.
(Glances)
You didn't reply.
Why didn't I reply?
How much water temperature do you drink?
I can adjust it for you.
You're so thoughtful.
(Cup not opened)
Still half asleep.
I might need to add some cold water.
Be careful.
(The water is hot)
Why is my voice like this?
(You first)
You sound like you're rapping.
I've finished getting water.
(Chen Hewen)
I'm done. Shall we go?
I noticed you've become more thoughtful.
No, I mean,
Zhao Xilun is really obsessed
with turmeric powder.
Like, from the very beginning...
He was into health and wellness stuff.
Yeah, like anti-inflammatory powders.
See you.
See you, guys.
Why is he speaking English again?
Just make it warm enough to drink.
400ml at 85 degrees,
plus
100ml at 25 degrees.
That'll be over 70 degrees.
Up to you.
You two are the English group.
I saw there are individual ones.
Try one.
(Searching)
It's gone.
Guess what I'm doing.
What's in your hand?
(Let me see)
You're looking for food.
I went to get ice cream.
(Walking away)
We're so sad.
Really so sad.
Come here, Meng.
(Leaving the kitchen)
(Wiping tears)
Don't cry.
I'm okay now.
Are you okay now?
(Sniffling)
Yeah, I'm okay now.
But your eyes look watery.
I'm better now, actually.
It's just that at that time,
because it
was that playground day.
Everyone probably
saw things differently.
Yeah.
From my perspective,
I just felt
like everyone seemed to
have someone else.
And at that time, I felt like I
was the extra person.
Then I was scared
that I might bother
you guys.
No.
How could you?
I really had that thought back then.
So I felt a little upset.
But later I realized it
was actually okay.
Today, I told myself
I absolutely won't shed a single tear.
(Trying to calm down)
Okay.
Do you want to talk about it?
Or
you can just sit here and eat for a bit?
I'll sit here and eat for a bit, okay?
Okay.
(Don't tell anyone)
I need to roast myself for a second.
I look so ugly when I cry, guys.
I was about to say you looked beautiful.
You looked good!
Yeah.
Then I looked at myself back then.
I cried like a zongzi.
I really looked like that!
Like a zongzi!
Really.
Why did all my facial features
bunch together?
You're super cute, okay?
It's okay. Keep going.
Two.
Do I have to give them?
Sun Bohan is pretty relaxed too.
Right? The way he sits
is so funny!
Yeah.
Yeah, Sun Bohan.
He's really relaxed.
He has that old money vibe.
Old money vibe!
No, it's so funny!
Do you have two people you want
to give them to?
Let's see.
I'm curious who Chen Hewen will give his to.
He'll definitely give one to you.
Who else?
(Who else?)
My gosh.
Did you expect him
to give one to you back then?
I think I was a little angry then.
Because of that daytime activity.
I'll just write a name.
Can't make her wait too long.
Oh my God.
That's how Cao Yiheng is?
Yeah, Cao Yiheng is really sweet.
Yeah.
They said Yu Yang has "husband energy".
There are guys outside all three dorms.
Is it Cao Yiheng?
No way.
I can't go out right now.
I'll open the door.
She said she can't come out right now.
She can't come out?
It really is Cao Yiheng.
I'm coming.
What is this?
That instant change of expression!
Wait.
The expression change was way too fast.
Cui Kaiyi.
That's hilarious.
Will you write my name?
(Glances)
Isn't that an obvious question?
You're testing me?
Of course I will.
These two are so funny.
(Handing over)
They gave one.
I remember Cui Kaiyi gave two.
The other one was for Zhao Xilun.
Because she knew Zhao Xilun
wouldn't give one to her.
She thought she had to give out two.
To two guys.
Yeah.
Come on.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go...
(Into your heart)
Oh my God.
(Yu Yang, Liang Renfang)
Yu Yang has this side too?
Never seen it before.
I've never seen it.
Me neither.
Oh my God.
Look.
Everyone gets two date tickets.
For two separate dates.
But it never said you
had to write two people,
right?
Zhao Xilun and I
totally misunderstood it.
(We thought we had to write two names)
He wrote Si's name.
Yeah.
I see.
(Then I'll cross it out)
Sun Bohan gives such a sense of security.
(Laughs)
I thought it'd be weird
to write someone else.
So I thought...
I'd just write Si, right?
How did you guys discuss it?
Back then,
Liang Renfang and I never thought
about writing a second person.
We only wanted to write one person.
Because we wrote it really quickly.
We wrote the name
right after getting the card.
Yeah, because you were very sure.
Yeah, we were pretty sure at that time.
I remember the three
of us talked about it.
I said back then...
You're only choosing one person.
Yeah, only one person.
I said I was going to give both
to one person.
Then Meng said she didn't know
who to give the second one to.
Yeah.
Then I said I'd give it to Chen Hewen.
Really.
I really gave it to Chen Hewen.
From my perspective,
I was a dummy.
I thought maybe nobody would choose him.
Really?
Because I really couldn't
reach you back then.
I had no idea
what you were feeling.
That's honestly how I felt.
That's so funny.
Really funny!
(Thirty minutes ago)
Meng.
So I don't hurt her...
Why are they whispering?
(Nods)
That's so funny.
It...
It would be better for her too.
Yeah.
But honestly,
my feelings here...
My mindset actually changed a little.
Because I wasn't sure
if he would choose me.
I thought,
if he didn't choose me,
I really needed
a chance to clear things up with him.
I might have chosen
the stargazing room or something.
That really could've happened.
I think so too.
Because at the playground,
I could already feel
his feelings were clear.
I felt like I had to
have a proper talk with him.
(Thirty minutes ago)
You two
are so cute.
(Looking at photos)
But why do I feel like you...
Do you think this photo
makes you look slimmer?
(Taking photos)
No, you're just naturally slimmer.
No, you're just a thin person.
(Smiles)
(Wu Siying)
Look at my blush.
Why are you laughing, Xing?
Xing is so funny.
No.
Her focus
is completely on my blush.
Blush?
(Wu Siying)
Why is this blush so red?
I'm crying from laughing.
Is the blush really the focus?
Sorry.
(Thirty minutes ago)
Maybe these two days I'll...
go find Liang Xiaoyu.
I'll talk
to her.
Talk things through.
Out of politeness,
I should at least tell her a little...
(Cui Yihang)
about my journey and thoughts.
Okay.
(Smiles)
Can I say that?
(Stares)
He even asked you.
It's okay to say it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Si, were you shy?
Si even shook her head.
(Thirty minutes ago)
No.
I wasn't.
Actually, since we
first started interacting,
there were signals.
But nothing felt very certain.
This time, I could feel
he was more certain.
Yeah, what he said
gave you a sense of security.
Yeah.
Maybe from that moment,
I started feeling more certain.
Si,
do you remember when we
talked on the balcony?
I remember.
So back then,
you only saw him as a friend?
At that moment, you did like him.
Yeah, I liked him.
And wanted to know him better.
That's when you became more certain.
Yeah, that's when we really
started understanding
each other.
We became more certain.
Yeah.
(Thirty minutes ago)
Mine looks so ugly.
Pretty ugly.
(Teasing)
You look better in person.
You think so too?
This photo made me look bad.
I think so too.
Don't you think I look better in person?
(Eye contact)
Were you happy back then?
Pretty happy.
I can tell.
Xing's
so funny.
I think from the beginning, he wanted
to get to know me slowly.
Then while getting to know me,
he realized I was someone
he wanted to know better.
That's when he started taking action.
He's different from Chen Hewen.
Very different.
(Thirty minutes ago)
Won't we scare him to death?
This is...
Let's go together.
Let's go.
He'll be thrilled.
Two beauties coming to see him.
(Heading to Chen Hewen's room)
(Uses her second card to invite Hewen)
Thanks.
(This is)
I was "drunk".
I'm not done writing yet.
You're not done? Keep writing.
I saw everyone else already...
I'll go first.
Make it good.
No problem.
Thanks.
(Quick interview)
Chen Hewen probably
(I'm really happy)
was going to find you.
(That's all you've got?)
Sha Yue'er, I feel like
(Anything else?)
he seemed a little distracted.
Thanks, everyone, for choosing me.
I'll definitely write them carefully.
I'll make sure to...
Okay.
Bye.
Good night.
Can we go back now?
I haven't written mine yet.
Wait for him.
He still has to write his.
Are you still deciding who
to give them to?
Didn't you finish writing them?
You just have to give them out.
I'll wait till they come upstairs.
I won't go downstairs.
They're probably chatting
or something.
I'm so torn.
I'm...
I'm waiting for the perfect chance
to give them out.
I still don't really understand.
Why did he hesitate so long
just to give an invitation card?
I feel like from this point,
he wasn't
as open and confident as before.
Yeah.
Was it because he saw how certain
Zhao Xilun was about you?
I think so.
I think he probably
needed a clearer response from you.
Only then could he keep moving forward.
(Glances)
(Looks back)
(Trips)
(Stops)
I was just waiting for him.
(Come on. Okay)
And he didn't come over.
He's taking photos.
(Let's sit on this giant banana)
You were waiting for his card, right?
(Sure)
Yeah.
Can you take a picture for us?
Sure, of course.
Of course.
Let's sit on this giant banana.
The three of us.
(Turns and leaves)
Sure.
(Are we each taking a corner?)
I couldn't take it anymore.
I got mad and left.
I waited there for so long.
If you had the courage to come,
then why didn't you?
Why was I still standing there?
I felt like he was ignoring me.
I was already upset at that moment.
Then he started calling out.
I didn't even know who he was calling.
He always gives me
this very unclear feeling.
So I wasn't really sure
about his feelings either.
And I didn't understand
why he waited until so late.
You felt like he was hesitating, right?
There were only 20 minutes left then.
Yeah.
He waited until really late.
Here.
Look at you, swimming in invitations.
(Chen Hewen and Liang Xiaoyu made a date)
No.
Nice.
(Stops)
Ask me.
So cute!
You actually told Chen Hewen to ask you.
Yeah, he took so long to ask me!
So I told him,
"Ask me."
You're so cute.
Seriously, we didn't see anything.
No.
- Didn't see anything at all.
- Didn't see.
But Chen Hewen saw it.
Luckily
you two made eye contact.
Sha Yue'er is actually very direct.
Yeah.
(Walks away)
You already gave out
your other invitation card?
I have one for you.
What about the other one?
You already gave it out?
Wait, did you only give out one?
Look!
Wow.
What annoys me the most is
he always asks me questions back.
That line really would make a girl mad.
Yeah.
And he does it every time.
Every time.
Yeah, you two are
on the "opposing side".
Actually,
a few days ago,
I wanted to tell you something.
Since I'm also getting
to know other guys...
Yeah.
It's okay if you get
to know other girls too.
What I'm trying to say is,
I didn't even need to tell you that
because you're already doing it.
When you said that to him,
you were just saying it out of anger.
When you told him
to get to know other girls,
It...
It wasn't out of anger.
I was just saying that
I also hadn't completely rejected Zhao Xilun.
I think it's his right
to get to know other girls.
But I was still a little upset.
Maybe because I
felt like he went
from being clear to unclear.
And after
opening the stargazing room,
it felt like he
wanted to know other people even more.
That's how it felt from my perspective.
I just think you're
a very considerate person.
But maybe you put your friends'
and everyone else's feelings
before
that person's.
That person?
I mean...
(Laughs out loud)
You're embarrassed
to say "before me".
Yeah.
Chen Hewen is holding back his laughter.
(Figure it out yourself.)
That's how it is.
(Smiles)
And then?
Can you stop smiling?
I'm not smiling.
You've been smiling this whole time.
I think being around you is exhausting.
That exhausting?
Very.
Because you can't tell
what I'm thinking sometimes.
Of course I can.
He can tell and still acts like this.
He might as well say he can't tell.
I think we can all tell
you want to be chosen wholeheartedly.
Yeah.
The kind of relationship we want
doesn't need so much politeness.
Yeah.
This is a dating show.
I understand you.
Deep down,
I'm actually pretty insecure.
I'm just being honest with you.
I'm insecure too.
I was really insecure as a kid.
Then why do you think
you're the only one?
Two people with low self-esteem.
(Have we ever talked about this?)
Finally opening up.
We still don't know
each other that well.
You never talk to me about this stuff.
So when we talk...
You think I don't listen?
You think I just like talking,
right?
No, Sha Yue'er.
Why are you...
Are you really gonna...
Make a fuss over this?
No one thinks you're making a fuss.
Feel it?
If you can't take it, just say it now.
But honestly,
I understand you.
When he said that,
I wanted to argue back too.
Yeah!
I understand you.
You know?
So I just feel like
it was really unbelievable.
You weren't angry at this point?
I was already angry!
Both of you are laughing
while being angry.
I was laughing because I was angry.
It felt like a joke.
Yeah, she was speechless
from being angry.
You were so speechless.
It was like...
Yeah.
Whose name did you write first?
Yours, of course.
You were happy?
Don't tell me you got comforted already.
No!
Impossible.
I'm not that easy to cheer up.
Okay.
We're talking with the door open.
So it should be fine.
I feel like you
had a "strong start, weak finish".
Because you got invited away.
I was...
I was about to explode mentally.
I was so real about my feelings.
Then tell me, busy person,
if I want to ask you out,
how far in advance do I need to book?
Fight for it. Don't you
know how to compete?
Only men who compete and fight
for what they want can find a partner.
The vibe between you two is hilarious.
I think so too!
This is so funny!
But that's honestly the truth.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That's honestly the truth.
If he doesn't fight for me,
I'll feel like
he's interested in someone else.
Yeah.
Like he doesn't care
about you that much.
Yeah.
But saying this to Chen Hewen
actually showed how serious
you were about him
at that moment, right?
Yeah. You really cared
about him.
I really do care about him.
Because I realized all my emotions
are affected by him.
But he gives me this feeling
that he wants to get close
but also wants to run away.
Or maybe he just wants
to compete with me.
You two are really
on the "opposing side".
That's so funny.
I wrote your name on my first card.
But you wrote her on your second card?
I had to give out both cards.
Then who else could I give it to?
I had no idea.
You could've given it to my roommate.
(Glances)
Cui Kaiyi?
Yeah.
Cui Kaiyi wrote it for Zhao Xilun.
Because she didn't want
to go the next day.
Didn't Cui Kaiyi give it to Zhao Xilun?
But he didn't understand.
He didn't get it.
Maybe he hasn't realized it yet.
Nervously picking at his fingers.
He's already feeling awkward.
I just wanted to know what you'd do.
Me?
I suddenly don't want
to write it for you anymore.
Why? It's just...
Because I'm someone who's easily
narrow-minded.
I'm petty like that.
Okay.
Then I understand you
a little better now.
Did I go too far with what I said today?
Sha Yue'er is still thinking about
(Outside)
how she felt back then.
(Sorry)
She must've felt really wronged.
I really didn't mean it.
Actually, I can feel it.
Because I probably just
wanted to explain my thoughts.
I didn't expect...
I'm sorry.
I'll get you some tissues.
Thanks.
It's okay.
Oh my gosh.
But this is the first time
I've seen Sha Yue'er's perspective.
I thought Sha Yue'er wasn't someone
who expressed herself much.
But she's actually
pretty straightforward.
Yeah.
You were really direct.
I think you already
showed me
a 100% certainty.
That's how firm your feelings were.
If I were the other person,
I would feel how serious you are.
So I understand why you felt hurt.
Really hurt.
Honestly,
if someone argued with me like that,
I'd just
lose my ability to say anything.
I was already speechless
when I got confronted at first.
Yeah.
Maybe he was also trying
to compete a little.
Yeah, you can tell.
That's why it ended up like this.
Maybe he was saying
the opposite of what he meant.
Oh gosh.
What if I didn't give you
an invitation card?
It's okay.
I accept it.
No problem.
I agree.
That's ridiculous!
Were you about to explode
from anger then?
Yeah!
But maybe he was saying that
out of anger.
That's the truth.
(Okay. Fine)
Gave him a look.
Sha Yue'er.
No.
The way he called "Sha Yue'er" twice
was kind of funny.
Yeah, I said it then too.
It was really funny.
Sha Yue'er.
When he called your name,
did you hear him?
I heard him.
I thought he would come after me.
But he just sat there.
Did you really want him
to come get you?
Of course I did!
If he had come after you,
would you have given him
the invitation card?
There would've been
a much higher chance.
If he didn't come, zero chance.
He didn't even give himself a way out.
Yeah.
And he didn't give me one either.
So you purposely ignored him?
Yeah.
Don't pay attention to him.
He didn't come out either.
He could've come out.
It was only a few steps away.
I was already pretty mad.
But then he called "Sha Yue'er" twice.
It made me want to laugh!
Sha Yue'er.
It had this "CEO boyfriend" vibe!
That's so funny!
When he said "no problem",
he was just acting tough.
Acting tough.
Yeah.
Okay.
No problem.
Laughing like a pig!
Sha Yue'er,
were you kneeling on the floor?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Why were you kneeling?
What's going on?
I'm crying.
Cui Kaiyi just finished showering.
Cui Kaiyi came out after her shower again?
Cui Kaiyi!
A familiar scene.
Cui Kaiyi went back to text you,
and you came again.
(Pet park)
Meng's date.
Meng.
So pretty.
Hi.
It's okay. She won't bite.
You can pet her.
(Gently)
His dog is actually really cute.
(It might want to play)
She's such an energetic dog.
We can take a few photos.
Rose, look at me!
(Pose)
The weather is so nice.
She really looked at me.
(Sit)
This pose is great.
Come on, look at the camera.
This photo of you looks great.
Right?
Yeah.
So beautiful.
Three, two, one.
This dog is really well-behaved.
The vibe is so nice.
(Kisses)
Yeah.
Actually,
I used to be scared of dogs.
But his dog is really well-behaved.
So I'm not scared anymore.
Look, she knows to look
at the camera for photos.
She even knows how
to look good in photos.
She's just...
Really smart.
She's pretty clever.
Yeah, really smart.
When we first met,
you were wearing a blue suit.
Hello.
Meng's eyes lit up.
Yeah.
Those sparkling eyes.
From my angle,
I could see your side profile.
So I thought you were different.
I really felt that
you were someone
with strong boundaries.
You were just
different when it came
to someone you liked.
Thank you for appreciating me.
Really.
Yeah, but...
Actually, I...
I can't return those feelings.
I feel like maybe
in each other's futures,
we should just be friends.
Just friends.
I hope
you can relax too.
(Relax)
Yeah, let's just be friends.
I'm taking back my feelings.
(Taking back my feelings)
Looking back at this scene now,
I feel like
this date
was my bravest moment in the house.
It's just that this relationship
was probably only from my side.
It wasn't mutual.
But I still think it
was something beautiful.
You were really brave.
Meng, you're truly an angel.
I'm afraid
if I'm too proactive,
he'll
feel scared.
I'm especially afraid
I'll pressure him too much.
Before,
I thought I was someone
who develops feelings over time.
But maybe I can fall
in love at first sight too.
(You were my love at first sight)
Because we're both The Courageous,
I hope
you can be a little braver.
And carry my courage with you.
To face
the future.
To face everything unknown
in the future.
Looking back at this now,
I still feel so moved.
It really was like that.
Actually, I noticed Zhao Xilun at that time.
His eyes were also filled with tears.
Yeah.
Yeah, I felt like he's
also a very emotional person.
Yeah.
Xing's moved again.
Yeah, because I saw how open Meng was.
After watching this,
I feel like Meng will definitely find
someone amazing.
Someone who will truly love you.
You deserve someone wonderful too.
Thank you, Xing.
Actually,
after I finished talking with Zhao Xilun,
I felt like
I could be more comfortable
in the house.
You finally cleared things up.
Yeah, like we truly talked things out.
He felt better too.
I felt better too.
It was the right decision.
I want to applaud myself.
And I managed to control
my emotions that day.
Applause.
Well done.
(Don't go anywhere. The next episode
is even more romantic.)